<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1. Projects on</title><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-projects/</link><description>Recent content in 1. Projects on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Fill-In-Simple-Schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Fill-In-Simple-Schedule/</guid><description>NPC Schedule NPC Schedule System Prototype Simple Schedule Schedule is built from an array of Scheduleables. These contain a time span that represents the start time and end time. Tasks can be searched for and added based on a required timespan from the Task Pool.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Fill-In-Simple-Task-Pool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Fill-In-Simple-Task-Pool/</guid><description>NPC Schedule NPC Schedule System Prototype Simple Task Pool Contains a list of all Task Pool Items available in the game. These contain time spans that represent the available start and end times. FindTask uses a time frame representing the start time and duration of available time to search for a task. If a task has a start time earlier than or the same as the start time in the time frame and has a duration that encompases the duration of the time frame, then the task is available to fill the request.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Ireena-Wynran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Ireena-Wynran/</guid><description> Characters</description></item><item><title/><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/NPC-Schedule-System-Prototype/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/NPC-Schedule-System-Prototype/</guid><description>NPC Scheduling System Prototype Area: NPC Schedule Interfaces ITaskPool ITaskPoolItem ISchedule IScheduleable ITimeFrame ITimeSolver ITask ITaskFilter IContext IPrioritySolver IAttendantSolver Implementations SimpleSchedule SimpleTaskPool TaskPoolBehaviour SimpleScheduleable SimpleTaskPoolItem SimpleTimeFrame SimpleTimeSolver SimplePrioritySolver SimpleAttendantSolver ManyFilter Example SimpleTask SimpleContext SimpleFilter</description></item><item><title/><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Research-Voice-Problems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Research-Voice-Problems/</guid><description>Video Editing I recorded 2 voicovers within a few minutes of each other in the same environment and the quality of each was completely different. I used</description></item><item><title/><link>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Switch-to-Davinci-Resolve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FedoraGameDev.github.io/1.-Projects/Switch-to-Davinci-Resolve/</guid><description>Video Editing Davinci has everything I need to edit videos. Olive may become an awesome open source alternative, however it&amp;rsquo;s still a few years out of scope.</description></item></channel></rss>